<idea-plugin version="2">
   <name>Gradle GUI</name>
   <id>Gradle GUI</id>
   <description>This provides a graphical representation of Gradle projects and tasks and allows execution of Gradle tasks
       directly within Idea. Frequently-used tasks can be added to the Favorites tab for quicker access. Output is shown in
       a separate panel allowing the main UI to be vertical and the output to be horizontal. This is the same UI as the UI
       embedded in Gradle itself.

       Note: you can assign keyboard shortcuts within Idea to re-execute the last gradle command and to
       execute gradle favorites. To do so, go to Idea's settings -> Keymap and select Other. In this list find commands
       prefixed with "Gradle: ". The favorites are keyed off of the display name so it can work across projects as long
       as their name is the same. 
   </description>
   <version>1.7</version>
   <change-notes>1.7: Fixing compatibility with Idea 12. Idea was logging exceptions due to icon size changes. This generated excessively large log files.</change-notes>
   <change-notes>1.6: Fixing compatibility with Idea 11 EAP build 110.492. GradleLibraryManager.INSTANCE was removed from Idea and this plugin threw an exception on startup.</change-notes>
   <change-notes>1.5: Fixing compatibility with Idea 11 EAP. This version is not compatible with Idea 10. The main panel is now displayed even if Gradle's path isn't defined in Idea. This allows you to load the UI once Gradle is configured. Updated the icon based on Gradle's website.</change-notes>
   <change-notes>1.4: Fixing compatibility with Idea 10.5.</change-notes>
   <change-notes>1.3: Fixing compatibility with Idea 10 EAP.</change-notes>
   <vendor url="http://wiki.github.com/gradle/gradle-intellij-gui/" email="user@gradle.codehaus.org" >Gradle</vendor>
   <idea-version since-build="123.72"/>
   <depends>org.intellij.groovy</depends>
   <depends>org.jetbrains.plugins.gradle</depends>

   <application-components>

       <component>
           <implementation-class>org.gradle.ideaplugin.ui.GradleUIApplicationComponent</implementation-class>
       </component>

   </application-components>

   <project-components>

       <component>
           <implementation-class>org.gradle.ideaplugin.ui.MainGradleComponent</implementation-class>
       </component>

       <component>
           <implementation-class>org.gradle.ideaplugin.ui.GradleOutputComponent</implementation-class>
       </component>

   </project-components>

   <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
      <projectService serviceInterface="org.gradle.ideaplugin.ui.GradleUISettings2"
                      serviceImplementation="org.gradle.ideaplugin.ui.GradleUISettings2"/>
  </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
